Md Faisal Hossain

Bangladesh



faisal.m13574@gmail.com



linkedin.com/in/md-faisal-878628202



https://faisal413.github.io/profile.com/

Summary

I am Faisal. And I am game Developer. Experienced Data Entry Operator with a demonstrated history of working in the government administration industry. Skilled in Microsoft Office, C (Programming Language), HTML(Hyper Text Markup Language), CSS (Cascading Style Sheets), JavaScript and Unity (game engine).

Experience



Game Developer

Unity Technologies Dec 2020 - Present (3 months +)



Data Entry Operator

Income Tax Department of UK Mar 2020 - Present (1 year +)

Education



Adarsha Pre-Cadet School

SSC

2020 - 2022



Adarsha Pre-Cadet School

JSC

2019 - 2019

Skills

Html • Cascading Style Sheets (CSS) • JavaScript • Logo Design • Python (Programming Language) • Adobe Photoshop • Adobe Illustrator • Microsoft Office • Unity • C#